Darron Lee with the Jets.
The wait is over. You get that Yeah, I'm
doing good. You get that trip to New
York. Let's go, bud. Let's do it. Let's
do it. Let's work, man. Get ready. Can't
wait to get you here and get to work.
I'm going to hand you to AG right now,
all right? DB, how you doing, brother?
How you doing, coach?
Man, I'm doing well. How are you doing?
That's the question. I'm I'm doing
great, man. I appreciate you.
Man, we appreciate you, brother. Listen
here, the wait is over. Now it's time to
get to work. Looking forward to you
getting out of that, man.
Congratulations. Congratulations, man.
Enjoy this night with your family, all
right? Oh boy, you talked to two really
good guys. David, congratulations.
>> How you doing? Thank you, man.
>> I'm doing I'm doing so much better than
now that I'm talking to you.
So, you're going to You're going to love
it here. You're going to love it here.
You're going to love your coach.
>> Coach, what's good, man? How you living?
I'm living larger than charge, big dog.
I just want to say hello, man.
We're sitting [laughter] in here. We're
excited as hell.
But that's good stuff.
>> Thank you.
>> Enjoy the night, David. We'll see you
tomorrow, all right?